we really appreciate you inviting us
over for dinner Athair yeah the gifts
were the stock it you can already tell
if this is going to they already are
hey where are the tickets anyway Charles
what the [ __ ] I thought you were
watching them I am hosting over the leg
Elena they'd help stays Manic get over
here and check this out you're not going
to believe your eyes no way I'm so close
to beating your high score here Manic
trust me this ain't something you're
going to wanna miss look down
okay you have a hole in your floor so
what man Acharya my God you are wasting
precious time oh I see what's going on
here the first thing I do is look down
and the next thing I know is that I'm
face full and Sonic the Hedgehog's but
Manic would I do that to you
I'm like your only friend okay fine
Knuckles why do you have this I'm
alright the whole was here when we
bought the house apparently the previous
owner beat his wife so there are holes
in a lot of walls a fair doesn't know
about this one it lets you see
everything that goes on down there
[Music]
heeey I sure hope nobody is watching me
poop that would be pretty embarrassing
okay so what do you think Manic pretty
cool no it's just [ __ ] weird what are
you saying
spying on people is just wrong
especially if they are taking a huge
smelly crap Monica though you were cool
but it turns out you're just another
square get out of my room
alright but I will be telling your
grandfather about this he has to know I
can't let you do that Manik
what the hell was at it came from
upstairs Manic and Mindy are probably
having sex on the roof again
can you kids see who's calling while
your uncle and now get the table ready
what's up Elena we are at five so say a
us are a weird telephonist kids they
said Isis a touchpads and whatnot they
cannot comprehend the telephony
this is a weird-looking cellphone why is
it so big who cares just grab it and
let's go back to the kitchen they it
stuck to this [ __ ] box
why kind of a cellphone is this I got a
pair of scissors why don't we just cut
it they that's a good idea sis now you
are thinking like a Hedgehog
mom I think we broke the cellphone
that's strange
why aren't they answering the phone well
I I guess they are just having so much
fun haha
not a problem for the old register I'll
just try calling again
pick up the phone you fat [ __ ] do my
bidding
[Music]
we're sorry you have reached a number
that has been disconnected or is no
longer in service if you feel you have
reached this recording in error please
check the number and try your call again
[Music]
thank you for doing the dishes but I can
take over now
you guys go enjoy yourselves it looks
like the Thanksgiving football game is
about to start you should go watch it I
know how white people love that [ __ ] you
know that sounds like a plan
eight what an availing definitely can't
wash teleme we told Terre Haute City of
course Charles just check the fringe
omegle yo le boot lid premium your way
been holding out on daddy I went yo big
boy
Knuckles can you come here your great
granddad needs a favor sure thing our
neighbor came by yesterday and told me
that he is going to shoot us if we don't
rake up all the leaves by tonight
take your girlfriend along and clean
that [ __ ] up so we don't get to cap in
our ass she's not my girlfriend grandad
she's just one of my [ __ ]
what stay mother a fire oh it's nothing
major really if Bo isn't related to me
c'mon what's what adding job well you
see I was just thinking about some stuff
does Knuckles get along with your
sister's kids like are they good friends
amen
isla partida I see that's good
Knuckles has a really hard time making
friends he gets depressed at this time
of year the cause he doesn't have a
mommy or daddy like the other kids
Aloha be parents what happened to them I
will tell you Charles
the story of his parents and how his
father and mother were taken away by the
Japanese Yakuza Knuckles father Jeremy
the Echidna was once a member of the
Yakuza but he gave up that life to
support his new family his new son
Knuckles of that being a Yakuza it isn't
something you can just walk away from
and one day the Yakuza came to collect
their debt
they're here the Yakuza my old coMrades
tomorrow anymore yatin are already
control negativeness
well that's no Coco anymore como una
material master I told you not to call
me that anymore not Kishida snake
k'tano tio tio Rico tuna Delta solid
Acadia
well there's no leader well can you miss
it by your another cigar sir OTO Dozo
what are they saying honey I can't
understand a single word don't worry
[ __ ] let me talk to them
oh my no I sattva Modi touching no tone
material still nakaoka gnarled aru what
did you say honey I couldn't understand
the [ __ ]
will you shut your [ __ ] mouth [ __ ]
what are you looking at you [ __ ] baby
you killed our Oh
oh my well here we bilko dah dah dah dah
dah
Nene an immense day you to stay at all
da are not - in Kentucky or there one
animal come on what's that Auditor what
are they saying now Jeremy they said if
we give them the $12 I owe them they
will leave and never return
oh thank Heavens I just gave you a $20
bill for the strip club remember you can
just give that to them no holy hell
Jeremy this is about the life of our
span can't you stop going to the damn
strip club for once in your life
well that's no kokyo anymore Kalyanam
Anthony ha ha you want my answer fine
then here's my answer
lift my big fat juicy butt cheeks
let us not either well can you miss
about your another smell get your hands
off of me
[Music]
please I beg of you let us go we have
nothing to do with this he's just a boy
he needs somebody to take care of him
dania not a dodo Russian Kentucky
[Music]
he hasn't raked any leaves for 13
minutes what do you think he's thinking
about the little [ __ ] is probably
crying because I put TNT in his
minecraft house yesterday I think one of
us should go talk with him I'll do it no
bro you're too fat
get going [ __ ] what about you we got
into a fight earlier and he tried to
shove a lightsaber up my butt damn
that's kind of sexy bro I'll try talking
to him he's probably just lonely since
he doesn't have cool sips like us hey
Knuckles how are you feeling
leave me alone that's not very
Thanksgiving you thing to say what's
bothering you
there's nothing bothering me absolutely
nothing nothing at all
[Music]
Sleet go back to the McDonald's bathroom
and get more toilet paper it feels like
daddy's gonna be here for a while
times must be tough for you dr. Robotnik
pooping in trash cans now [ __ ] there's
people here who would have thought you'd
fall so low as to crap in strangers
trash cans pathetic fat boy the evil
emperor of evil dr. Robotnik can poop
where he damn well pleases your reign of
terror was over just now when I caught
you taking a huge dump get off this
property before I embarrass you in front
of all my friends let's see if you can
do that before I crush your head between
my fat butt cheeks but Sir today is
Thanksgiving the day of peace and love
we should put our grudges aside even if
it is just for today whatever I don't
give a [ __ ] come on [ __ ] let's go
inside and get some turkey with mashed
potatoes and green beans
stop right there family you can't just
go inside without permission
unfortunately for you blue boy I can
subSonic my man how's my best friend
doing on this fine afternoon
oh hey Trevor um what are you doing here
haha what do you think I'm doing here
Sonic it's Thanksgiving and [ __ ]
everyone knows you spend Thanksgiving
with your friends and family and you're
like the only friend I've got and [ __ ]
we tight as [ __ ] I heard you were
throwing a Thanksgiving party with a
bunch of friends you must have forgotten
to give me an invite I tried calling you
but you didn't pick up oh so that was
you who tried to call us on the phone
kind of broke
no offense Trevor but don't you think
you should spend Thanksgiving with I
don't know your family ha ha what are
you talking about Sonic you know my
parents are dead as [ __ ] besides you're
like the only real friend that I have
you and I were were like family and [ __ ]
don't you remember when we fought
together as freedom fighters beating
Robotnik's ass of course I remember
Trevor but that was a long time ago you
and I don't talk that much anymore come
on Sonic what are you talking about
we're like best buds I mean I would suck
your balls if you sucked mine
listen Trevor I don't really know how to
say this without sounding like an
[ __ ] but [ __ ] I didn't invite you
because we are not friends nobody likes
you Trevor
come on Sonic you you don't actually
mean that actually I do and I think it's
time for you to leave Sonic don't do
this do you want me to suck your balls
why the [ __ ] are you keep trying to suck
my smelly balls I mean all I'm saying is
that we are best friends if you want me
to I'll suck your balls
Trevor just go home okay before you make
this even more awkward if you want to
suck my balls just get a couple of blue
gum balls out of the vending machine
down the street it's basically the same
thing
[Music]
you
Sonic you son of a [ __ ] how dare you
invite him how dare you invite that
orange demon you didn't invite me your
best friend and yet you invited Mingo
that bastard killed my parents
your parents had it coming they had a
bounty on their heads for a long time I
was only taking out the trash if I
didn't do it somebody else would have
eventually [ __ ] if I knew you were
going to bother me with this yours later
maybe I should have killed you then too
in fact maybe I should finish what I
started and shove my fist up your ass
you [ __ ] hippie
your parents brought their deaths upon
themselves when they attempted to rape
dr. Robotnik it wasn't anything personal
I was only doing my job and protecting
my round Overlord from the vile monsters
that are your parents
you're lying my parents were not
monsters they were amazing people and
sexy that's right
you will never know how they really work
poor boy you were a poopie covered baby
back then I thought I told all my
servants to go home for the night
whoever the [ __ ] that is you're fired
open the [ __ ] door right now old man
where I'm going to knock this [ __ ] down
myself yeah open up right now your fat
ass we're gonna rape your ass we are
gonna get revenge for all the mobiums
that you killed by raping your fat ass
Hey I remember those voices you're those
hippies whose tent I burned down while
you two were still [ __ ] inside of it
if you think I'm coming out you're crazy
I don't think he's gonna come out [ __ ]
stand back I'm gonna give it all I got
you got it baby how about a little kiss
for good luck
give your [ __ ] some sugar daddy
[Music]
will you stop crying you're a [ __ ] the
baby can't you see mommy is trying to
get on buddy's good side so that daddy
will [ __ ] mommy got in the ass tonight
[Music]
dingle speaking what's wrong Robotnik
why are you using the emergency bathroom
telephone
do you have explosive diarrhea again
that's time too hot no using face I need
you to get down here immediately
there are these two scruffy looking men
here and they're trying to rape me
you
then go where the [ __ ] are you going
it's the middle of the night come back
to bed
don't worry about it Sleet go back to
Sleet
Robotnik's in trouble but I can take
care of it I found them says we got him
have fat-ass me and my sister are gonna
rape you good job bro
drag that son of a [ __ ] out I'm gonna
suck his [ __ ] balls mission
accomplished
sir the intruders have been taken care
of but what should I do about their baby
what they brought a [ __ ] baby with
them I dunno just throw it out the
window or something
you
see you at school tomorrow Trevor I
gotta go inside and take a [ __ ]
Sonic please wait please don't go don't
leave me Sonic please open up please
I'll do anything just let me inside I
don't have any other friends I I'll suck
your balls bro are you sure we should
just leave him out there it's
Thanksgiving what if he really has no
other friends or family to go to Manic
that [ __ ] just tried to suck my
[ __ ] balls
I'm talking about your past that [ __ ]
ball [ __ ] oh yeah did you see that
Charles did you [ __ ] see that shot
none mark did go these are all say that
so that was pretty damn bitchin
blackBell player is so [ __ ] tight a
machine
what in God's name are you talking about
Charles that was the enemy team who just
scored wait hold on a damn minute
could it be that you don't know the
rules to basketball Charles you are
pooping on my butt how do you call
yourself a man and not know the rules to
basketball why a man who doesn't play
basketball isn't even a man at all next
thing you'll be telling me is that you
don't even beat women when they don't
make your ham and cheese sandwiches and
pizza rolls fast enough uh of course
taking out the rulest OS kid buy him a
ballast or mud
he was hosting kena would this be a
Spanky Dantas trellis to it and what
destructed Charles be honest with me are
you lying because you're jealous of my
manliness
yes you are but it's okay I don't blame
you after all I am what every man should
strive to be
I am muscular and I have fought in many
wars women want me and men fear me but
nobody can tame me because I am a
[ __ ] man yes you will never be as
mentally as me no one will but don't let
that fact discourage you every man
starts somewhere I just got a head start
in life compared to the rest of you I
learned early on that by beating women
and playing basketball is how a man wins
at life perhaps some day like when you
read the rules to basketball you will
learn this [ __ ] too
damn the baloney smells so [ __ ] good
I wonder if it's done cooking
Oh baby that is the [ __ ] tits
I just wanna shove that in my [ __ ]
butt are you for real
he's cooking Bologna for Thanksgiving
instead of a cookie pathetic oh my God
like is his family bald or something
that's so funny
I gotta film this end show it to my
friends smile for the camera
[ __ ] haha he's turning away he must be
embarrassed
hahaha dumb [ __ ] oh my God he fell over
[Laughter]
at a [ __ ] up are you alright yo twas all
the way a cement of the old said this
elderly man opens his from a toast for
the only life and this is Roger or a pie
is keenness okay boomer thanks Charles I
appreciate it but I can handle this
I'm sure I can come up with something
the kids will like okay I think what are
you going in on your Oh what am I going
to do those kids were right I don't have
enough money to feed all of us should I
just send everyone home
huh there's a huge sack on the kitchen
window but where did it come form
it seems to be made out of special
Japanese fabric I wonder what's inside
well these are Japanese bento boxes and
there is enough for everyone
oh yeah this is the real deal who in the
world brought these
you
[Music]
now who's ready for the best
Thanksgiving dinner ever
ah speaking
[Music]
so
to the crime
[Music]
it's your sleeve
[Applause]
[Music]